// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!
module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'In Thai Culture it is considered rude to:', 
      a: 'Wink at a stranger', 
      b: 'Touch someone on the  head',
      c: 'Step on a crack in a temple',
      d: 'Say the informal word for "cow"',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'In the story of Joseph and his Coat (Kimono) of many colors what did Joseph dream of?', 
      a: '7 fat cows and 7 lean cows', 
      b: '7 healthy sheaves of corn',
      c: 'a magnificent coat',
      d: 'Bowing stars and sheaves',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'KTM Dirt Bikes come exclusively in this color', 
      a: 'White', 
      b: 'Blue',
      c: 'Red',
      d: 'Orange',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'The Cleveland Indians have the longest CURRENT World Series drought at 71 years. What team has the record for longest drought in MLB history?', 
      a: 'The Yankees 77 years', 
      b: 'The Red Sox 85 Years',
      c: 'The Cubs 107 years',
      d: 'The Tigers 111 years',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'The Label that first signed Lil Wayne was?', 
      a: 'Cash Money', 
      b: 'Rap-a-Lot',
      c: 'Def Jam',
      d: 'Death Row',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Lil Wayne was signed to Cash Money at what lil age?', 
      a: '7', 
      b: '9',
      c: '11',
      d: '13',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'After getting a formal full-time offer at the ed of his Clearhead internship Brady made what celebratory purchase?', 
      a: 'Flight to Los Angeles', 
      b: 'Harley Motorcycle',
      c: 'Triumph Motorcycle',
      d: '1991 BMW with 200k mi',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Brady went to high school with this Clearheader', 
      a: 'Elliot Wenstrup', 
      b: 'Ryan Abelman',
      c: 'Cara Daniels',
      d: 'AJ',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Brady has had this many birthdays due to his leap year birthday', 
      a: '4', 
      b: '7',
      c: '8',
      d: '9',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'The Cleveland Browns are Named After', 
      a: 'NFL Legend Jim Brown', 
      b: 'Football coach Paul Brown',
      c: 'The color',
      d: 'A loveable stray dog',
      answer: 'b'
    }
  ]
};